The Other Lamb is a horror, drama, thriller film
directed by Małgorzata Szumowska.
For her entire life, the cult she was born into has
been all that teenage Selah has known.
Along with a band of similarly cloistered young women she lives seemingly unstuck in time, cut off from modern society in a remote
forest commune presided over by a man called Shepherd, a controlling, messiah-like figure with a frightening dark side.
But when her insular world is rocked by a series of nightmarish visions and disturbing revelations, Selah begins to
question everything about her existence—including her allegiance to the increasingly dangerous Shepherd.
Selah, played by Raffey Cassidy.
Shepherd, played by Michiel Huisman.
Sarah, played by Denise Gough.
Adriel, played by Eve Connolly.
Hanna, played by Kelly Campbell.
Eloise, played by Isabelle Connolly.
The Other Lamb is a 2019 horror film directed by
Małgorzata Szumowska and written by C.S.
It stars Raffey Cassidy, Michiel Huisman and Denise Gough.
The film explores themes of affectation, polygamy, forest, birth, death.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.